EVAN ST MARTIN

Junior Web Developer

Minneapolis, United States 6125016802 · evanstm011@gmail.com

PORTFOLIO, GITHUB, LinkedIn

Skills

React

JavaScript

HTML5

CSS3

Bootstrap

Node.js

MySQL

MongoDB

Git

Profile

I am a passionate self-taught web developer who loves anything tech. I have spent the past two years+ teaching myself how to code in JavaScript and build full stack web applications through Udemy courses, YouTube and other resources. I am particularly interested in front-end development. I love tinkering with CSS/HTML and designing cool websites. I have also dabbled in Swift and SwiftUI and I am currently learning how to build basic iOS applications. My goal is get my foot in the door and take on a junior developer role. I am excited for the new challenges that await me.

Employment History

Bartender, Landmark Center, Saint Paul

August 2018 - December 2020

This is a weekend gig where I served large events such as weddings, festivals and galas. During my time here I developed great costumer service skills and learned to remain calm during pure chaos.

Project Manager/ Production Team, Straighline House Painting MN

May 2015 - March 2020

This is a small business I worked for where I served a multifaceted role. Some examples: I worked as a sales associate, a painter, I managed full projects making sure the company took care of all of the costumer needs, so on. I learned a lot about business and project management during my time there.

Store Manager, Juice So Good, Minneapolis

January 2017 — January 2018

Similar to my role at Straightline I managed a store front making sure everything was ready in the morning. I made sure employees shifts were covered and all the product was ready for sell throughout the day. I also helped work register and worked directly with the company owners.

Education

Diploma, Highland Park Senior Highschool, Saint Paul

September 2007 - June 2011